

ALİ EFE BOZDAŞ



ali.1753.efe.2002@gmail.com

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/ali-efe-bozdas/

https://github.com/alifboz

https://tryhackme.com/p/alifkiller3

Objective

I have a strong tendency for a career in Cyber Security. To be sure, I'd like to experience the actual work environment. I hope that this internship will provide me a realistic ciew of the profession together with the behaviors and skilld necessary for success.

Education

Firat University Digital Forensics Engineering 10/2020-present Hatice Güzelcan Anadolu Lisesi 2016-2020

Projects

Blog Site With Laravel 2022-present

https://github.com/alifboz/Laravel_Login_Register_Page

- · Project of combining pieces of paper with image processing and artificial intelligence 2022-present
- 'TravelApp' aplication with Java in IEEE Firat Mobile App. Team (https://github.com/IEEEFiratComputerSociety/TravelApp)

Experience

 IEEE Firat Computer Society Committee / Cyber Security Team Leader 2021-22 I prepared and trained a Cybersecurity training path for team members.

• IEEE Firat Computer Society Committee / Mobile Application With Java Team Member 2020-21

I developed the main page and Login/Registration page of the TravelApp application by actively participating in the team.

C language instructor for my Class2020

I taught classmates algorithm and programming with C

Work **Experience**

· Founder of @deepoceancode

Since I have observed that students cannot discover and know where and how to head, I wanted to open a door for them to do something and win. My main goal in Deep Ocean Code is to generate value. My goal is to gather people's efforts in various fields such as cyber security, game programming, mobile application programming under one roof. On this way, I discovered that I could create Turkish resources in cyber security and other fields. I will continue to learn, teach, grow and develop Deep Ocean Code with firm steps.

- https://medium.com/@deepoceancode
- https://www.instagram.com/deepoceancode/

Skills / **Hobbies**

- Linux •••

- Entrepreneurship
- Historical literacy
- English
- C, C++ •••
- HTML-CSS
- Active Learning
- Python
- - Bocce Team Member 2017-2019
- Financial literacy
- E-commerce

